Finding Aid for the Collection of Television Film Scripts PASC.0074
UCLA Library Special Collections
Collection of Television Film Scripts
1967-[ongoing]
UCLA Library Special Collections
PASC.0074
119.0 linear feet (239 boxes)
Collection consists of scripts for films made for television.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942328723606533
Biography/History
American television networks began made-for-television movies in late 1964; by the early-1970s they had become a mainstay of network programming. Over the years, the range of movie offerings have been on par with theatrical film releases, within restricted timelines and budgets. Ultimately, television movies provided a venue for topical or controversial themes, not deemed appropriate for regularly scheduled network programing. The flexible time constraints of the medium made it possible to present full-legnth filmed versions of popular literary works, particularly through the TV mini-series.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of scripts for films made for television. Includes scripts for TV movies broadcast on various networks including ABC, CBS, HBO, NBC, and Showtime. Also includes scripts for television specials and mini-series. Among the many productions represented in the collection are All Quiet on the Western Front, Evita, Gideon's Trumpet, The Miracle Worker, Murder in Mississippi, Something About Amelia, Special Bulletin, and A Woman Called Golda
Organization and Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically by production title.
Related Material
Collection of Television Series Scripts (Collection 81). UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, UCLA.
Television Plays; Television scripts; Made-for-TV movies
- 21 HOURS AT MUNICH, (4/12/1976) (Box > 3)
  General note
  Writers: Hume, Edward
- A.D. (PART I: THE LIGHT), (4/18/1983) (Box > 35)
- A.D. (PART II: THE TIDE), (4/18/1983) (Box > 35)
- A.D. (PART III: THE WIND), (4/18/1983) (Box > 35)
- A.D. (PART IV: THE FIRE), (4/18/1983) (Box > 35)
- ABDUCTED: A FATHER'S LOVE, (8/29/1995) (Box >218)
  Writers: Oliansky, Joel
- ABDUCTION OF KARI SWENSON (THE), (7/20/1986) (Box >128)
  Writers: Gray, William
- ABDUCTION OF SAINT ANNE (THE), (11/21/1974) (Box >161)
- ACADEMY AWARDS (60th Annual Special), (no date) (Box >224)
- ACCEPTABLE RISK, (11/18/1985) (Box >191)
  Writers: Gluck, Marvin A
- ACORN PEOPLE (THE), (6/26/1980) (Box >122)
  Writers: Tewkesbury, Joan
- ACT OF LOVE, (3/31/1980) (Box >153)
  Writers: de Guzman, Michael; Mitchel, Paige
- ACT OF VENGEANCE, (no date) (Box >157)
  Writers: Spencer, Scott
- ADAM, (5/17/1983) (Box > 26)
- ADVOCATE'S DEVIL (THE), (11/6/1996) (Box >219)
  Writers: Sadwith, James
- AFFAIR (THE), (7/31/1973) (Box >106)
  Writers: Turner, Barbara
- AFTER THE PROMISE, (no date) (Box > 13)
- AFTERMATH: A TEST OF LOVE, (3/10/1990) (Box >126)
  Writers: Goodell, Gregory; Kinder, Gary
- AGAINST THE WALL, (5/4/1993) (Box >199)
  Writers: Hutchinson, Ron
- AIN'T MISBEHAVIN' (Special), (no date) (Box >237)
- ALAMO (THE): THIRTEEN DAYS TO GLORY, (12/2/1985) (Box >145)
  Writers: Morrill, Norman McLeod; Ware, Clyde
- ALAMO (THE): THIRTEEN DAYS TO GLORY, (6/26/1986) (Box >146)
- ALAN KING'S WONDERFUL WORLD OF AGGRAVATION, (11/20/1968) (Box >252)
  Writers: Bobrick, Sam; Clark, Ron
- ALEXANDER: THE OTHER SIDE OF DAWN, (2/16/1977) (Box >158)
  Writers: Dallenbach, Walter; Young, Dalene
- ALIENS ARE COMING (THE), (6/29/1979) (Box > 71)
  Writers: Lenski, Robert W.
- ALL GOD'S CHILDREN (FORMERLY: AN ECLIPSE OF REASON), (12/3/1979) (Box >103)
  Writers: Blinn, William
- ALL LIES END IN MURDER, (no date) (Box >210)
  Writers: Weisberg, Lynn Mamet
- ALL QUIET AT THE WESTERN FRONT, (9/20/1978) (Box > 35)
  Writers: Monash, P.
- ALMOST GROWN, (8/20/1987) (Box > 66)
  Writers: Chase, David; Konner, Lawrence
- ALWAYS REMEMBER I LOVE YOU, (8/28/1990) (Box >172)
  Writers: Radkoff, Vivienne
- AMAZING HOWARD HUGHES (THE), (11/5/1976) (Box >135)
  Writers: Gay, John
- AMAZING MR. HUGHES (THE), (11/26/1976) (Box >155)
- AMAZING MR. HUGHES (THE) (PART II), (11/26/1976) (Box >155)
- AMAZONS, (no date) (Box > 28)
- AMAZONS, (10/10/1983) (Box >197)
  Writers: Levinson, David
- AMBUSH MURDERS (THE), (5/26/1981) (Box > 94)
  Writers: Kayden, Tony
- AMELIA, (4/21/1976) (Box >203)
  Writers: Sobieski, Carol
- AMELIA EARHART, (4/1/1976) (Box > 85)
- AMERICAN CLOCK (THE), (10/1/1993) (Box >215)
  Writers: Galati, Frank; Miller, Arthur (based on)
- AMERICAN HARVEST, (4/1/1985) (Box > 92)
  Writers: Simon, Ronnie; Nanus, Susan
- AMERICAN MUSIC AWARDS (THE) (1980 Special), (no date) (Box >237)
- AMERICAN RIVER, (3/6/1989) (Box > 76)
  Writers: Huyck, Willard; Katz, Gloria
- AMERICA'S TRIBUTE TO BOB HOPE (Special), (no date) (Box >234)
- AMERIKA (BOOK I), (10/12/1985) (Box > 29)
  Writers: WRYE, DONALD
- AMERIKA (BOOK II), (10/27/1985) (Box > 29)
- AMERIKA (BOOK III), (11/14/1985) (Box > 29)
- AMOS, (5/14/1984) (Box > 57)
  Writers: Kramer, Richard
- ANATOMY OF AN ILLNESS, (no date) (Box > 28)
- AND BABY MAKES SIX, (6/3/1980) (Box >108)
  Writers: List, Shelley
- AND BABY MAKES SIX, (3/6/1979) (Box >171)
- AND I ALONE SURVIVED, (6/19/1978) (Box >115)
  Writers: Slate, Lane
- AND THE BAND PLAYED ON, (3/12/1992) (Box >160)
  Writers: Schulman, Arnold; Shilts, Randy
- AND THE BAND PLAYED ON, (1/4/1993) (Box >200)
  Writers: Schulman, Arnold
- ANGEL DUSTED, (11/21/1980) (Box >167)
  Writers: Craviotto, Darlene
- ANGEL DUSTED, (10/5/1980) (Box > 99)
- ANGEL ON MY SHOULDER, (no date) (Box > 28)
- ANGEL ON MY SHOULDER, (7/10/1978) (Box >143)
- ANNA KARENINA, (2/1/1983) (Box >174)
  Writers: Goldman, James
- ANOTHER WOMAN'S CHILD, (6/3/1982) (Box >149)
  Writers: Bromberg, Conrad
- APOCALYPSE WATCH (THE), (8/6/1996) (Box >218)
  Writers: Goldsmith, John; Canaan, Christopher
- APPOINTMENT AT HIGHBRIDGE, (no date) (Box >198)
  Writers: Martin, Quinn
- ARE YOU IN THE HOUSE ALONE?, (1/30/1978) (Box >141)
  Writers: Parker, Judith
- ARE YOU IN THE HOUSE ALONE?, (4/18/1978) (Box >120)
- ARTHUR THE KING, (11/14/1982) (Box >116)
  Writers: Wyles, J. David; Karp, David
- AS SUMMERS DIE, (7/19/1985) (Box > 26)
- ATF, (12/17/1996) (Box >256)
  Writers: Cornwell, Patricia
- ATTICA, (9/19/1979) (Box > 36)
  Writers: Wicker, T.
- ATTICA, (10/20/1979) (Box >168)
  Writers: Henerson, James; Wicker, Tom
- ATTICA: LINE OF FIRE, (9/16/1992) (Box >138)
- ATTICA: LINE OF FIRE, (12/18/1992) (Box >138)
- AUNT MARY, (11/13/1979) (Box > 97)
  Writers: Prelutsky, Burt
- AUNT MARY, (4/18/1979) (Box > 24)
- AURORA, (12/22/1983) (Box >135)
  Writers: McGreevey, John
- AUTOBIOGRAPHY OF MISS JANE PITTMAN (THE), (8/15/1973) (Box >176)
  Writers: Wynn, Tracy Keenan
- AWAKENING OF CANDRA (THE), (4/6/1981) (Box >107)
  Writers: Lazarus, Tom
- B.R.A.T. PATROL, (6/24/1985) (Box >184)
  Writers: Carter, Chris
- BABE, (no date) (Box > 28)
- BABE, (10/24/1974) (Box > 88)
  Writers: Lee, Joanna
- BABE: THE STORY OF BABE, (3/19/1975) (Box >178)
- BABY M, (12/24/1987) (Box >173)
- BABY SNATCHER, (12/9/1991) (Box >123)
  Writers: Rhinehart, Susan
- BABYSITTER (THE), (2/27/1980) (Box > 74)
- BACK TO BACK, (6/19/1995) (Box >207)
  Writers: Nygard, Roger; Keith, Lloyd
- BACKSTAIRS AT THE WHITE HOUSE, (4/28/1978) (Box >134)
  Writers: Bagni, Gwen; Dubov, Paul
- BAD RONALD, (6/18/1974) (Box > 87)
  Writers: Marin, Andrew Peter; Vance, John Holbrook
- BADGE OF THE ASSASSIN, (1/10/1985) (Box >114)
  Writers: Roman, Lawrence
- BAIT (THE), (12/30/1972) (Box >119)
  Writers: Mankiewicz, Don M.; Cotler, Gordon
- BAJA OKLAHOMA, (5/23/1987) (Box > 30)
  Writers: ROTH, BOBBY
- BARBARIANS AT THE GATE, (5/6/1992) (Box >200)
  Writers: Gelbart, Larry
- BARBARY COAST (THE), (2/28/1975) (Box > 69)
  Writers: Heyes, Douglas
- BARON AND THE KID (THE), (5/11/1984) (Box >181)
  Writers: Stratton, Bill
- BARRY SEAL, (10/25/1990) (Box > 90)
  Writers: Young, Roger
- BASEBALL IN BLACK AND WHITE, (8/1/1995) (Box >247)
  Writers: Himmelstein, David
- BATTERED, (3/3/1978) (Box >154)
  Writers: Grassle, Karen; Sears, Cynthia
- BATTLING FOR BABY, (5/6/1991) (Box >215)
  Writers: Silvers, Nancy
- BEASTS ARE ON THE STREETS (THE), (9/21/1977) (Box >110)
  Writers: Heath, Laurence
- BEFORE AND AFTER, (6/18/1979) (Box >195)
  Writers: Brooks, Hindi; Henerson, Jim
- BEFORE WOMEN HAD WINGS, (1/16/1997) (Box >219)
  Writers: Fowler, Connie May
- BELARAS SECRET (THE), (8/27/1984) (Box >218)
  Writers: Ruben, Albert
- BELLES OF BLEECKER STREET, (1/19/1990) (Box > 86)
  Writers: Brandstein, Eve; Beatts, Anne
- BERLIN TUNNEL 21, (7/16/1979) (Box > 36)
  Writers: Gay, J.
- BEST INTENTIONS, (5/9/1990) (Box > 89)
  Writers: Wesley, Richard
- BEST KEPT SECRETS, (12/29/1983) (Box >153)
  Writers: Smith, April
- BEST LITTLE GIRL IN THE WORLD (THE), (12/1/1980) (Box >100)
  Writers: Moessinger, David; Freedman, Jerrold
- BEST LITTLE GIRL IN THE WORLD (THE), (6/26/1980) (Box > 90)
  Writers: Moessinger, David; Freedman, J.; Levenkron, S.
- BEST PLACE TO BE (THE) (PART I), (8/31/1978) (Box >136)
  Writers: Whitmore, Stanford
- BEST PLACE TO BE (THE) (PART II), (8/31/1978) (Box >136)
- BETRAYAL, (4/15/1974) (Box >105)
  Writers: Miller, James M.
- BETRAYED BY INNOCENCE, (no date) (Box > 36)
  Writers: Coopersmith, J.; Bostwick, Barry
- BETRAYED BY INNOCENCE, (11/8/1985) (Box >161)
- BETTY FORD STORY (THE), (5/23/1986) (Box > 8)
  Writers: Hall, Karen
- BETWEEN LOVE AND HATE, (10/13/1992) (Box >212)
  Writers: Hawkins, D. Victor; Nelson, Tom
- BEULAH LAND, (8/29/1979) (Box >134)
  Writers: Miller, J.P.
- BEVERLY HILLS COWGIRL BLUES, (no date) (Box > 95)
  Writers: Husky, Rick
- BEYOND AND AFTER, (no date) (Box > 83)
  Writers: Brooks, Hindi
- BEYOND OBSESSION, (11/19/1992) (Box >216)
  Writers: Bostwick-Singer, Eugenia; Singer, Raymond
- BEYOND THE BERMUDA TRIANGLE, (3/7/1975) (Box >165)
  Writers: McDaniel, Charles A.
- BEYOND THE LAW, (no date) (Box >213)
  Writers: Degas, Andre
- BEYOND THE SHADOW, (no date) (Box >204)
  Writers: Ferguson, Larry
- BEYOND WITCH MOUNTAIN, (11/9/1981) (Box > 36)
  Writers: Young, R.M.
- BIG BAD JOHN ("A RIDE ON HAROLD'S NOSE"), (3/16/1983) (Box > 72)
  Writers: Barrett, James Lee
- BIG BLACK PILL (THE), (10/17/1980) (Box >114)
  Writers: Butler, Michael
- BIG JAKE, (no date) (Box > 65)
  Writers: Fink, Harry Julian; Fink, R. M.
- BILL (FORMERLY: WHOSE BROTHER, WHOSE KEEPER), (11/26/1980) (Box > 18)
  Writers: Blechman, Corey
- BILL (FORMERLY: WHOSE BROTHER, WHOSE KEEPER), (9/12/1980) (Box > 71)
- BILL: ON HIS OWN, (9/1/1982) (Box > 87)
  Writers: Morrow, Barry
- BILL: ON HIS OWN, (11/9/1983) (Box > 92)
- BILL: ON HIS OWN, (11/29/1982) (Box > 36)
  Writers: Morrow, B.
- BIRDMEN (THE), (7/12/1971) (Box >174)
  Writers: Kidd, David
- BIRDS OF PREY, (9/5/1972) (Box >135)
  Writers: Boris, Bob
- BIRTH OF THE BEATLES (THE), (2/1/1979) (Box >196)
  Writers: Kurland, John
- BITTER HARVEST, (9/23/1980) (Box > 36)
  Writers: Friedenberg, R.
- BLACKOUT, (7/28/1985) (Box > 28)
- BLACKOUT, (8/25/1983) (Box > 91)
  Writers: Ambrose, David
- BLACKOUT, (1/1/1985) (Box > 87)
  Writers: Ambrose, David E.
- BLADE IN HONG KONG, (11/28/1984) (Box >157)
  Writers: Cotler, Gordon
- BLIND FAITH, (3/15/1996) (Box >256)
  Writers: Military, Frank
- BLIND FAITH (PART I), (8/21/1989) (Box > 75)
- BLIND FAITH (PART II), (8/29/1989) (Box > 75)
- BLIND JUSTICE, (2/12/1994) (Box >200)
  Writers: Knauf, Daniel
- BLIND JUSTICE, (1/19/1993) (Box >213)
- BLIND WITNESS, (5/1/1989) (Box >186)
  Writers: Stevens, Edmond
- BLOOD AND ORCHIDS, (7/30/1984) (Box > 37)
  Writers: Shagan, S.
- BLOOD AND ORCHIDS, (6/26/1985) (Box > 37)
  Writers: Katlov, N.
- BLOOD FEUD, (10/6/1982) (Box > 37)
  Writers: Boris, R.
- BLOOD SPORT, (8/8/1973) (Box >106)
  Writers: Freedman, Jerrold
- BLOOD TIES, (9/12/1990) (Box > 86)
  Writers: Shapiro, Richard
- BLOODHOUNDS OF BROADWAY (THE), (7/22/1987) (Box > 17)
- BLUE AND THE GRAY (THE) (PARTS I AND II), (4/14/1981) (Box > 37)
  Writers: Hunter, I.M.
- BLUE KNIGHT (THE), (6/5/1973) (Box >176)
  Writers: Neuman, E. Jack; Wambaugh, Joseph
- BLUE LIGHTNING (THE), (11/15/1985) (Box >212)
  Writers: Kelley, William
- BLUES SESSION (Special), (no date) (Box >235)
- BORN BEAUTIFUL, (3/30/1982) (Box >150)
  Writers: Goldemberg, Rose Leiman
- BORN BEAUTIFUL, (2/9/1982) (Box > 3)
- BORN INNOCENT, (7/18/1974) (Box >105)
  Writers: DiPego, Gerald
- BORN TO RUN, (1/4/1993) (Box >209)
  Writers: Badat, R.M.
- BOUNTY MAN (THE), (6/1/1972) (Box >111)
  Writers: Byrnes, Jim
- BOY IN THE PLASTIC BUBBLE (THE), (8/10/1976) (Box >166)
  Writers: Stewart, Douglas Day
- BOY WHO DRANK TOO MUCH (THE), (3/16/1979) (Box >190)
  Writers: DeBlasio, Edward
- BRASS, (no date) (Box > 74)
- BRASS TARGET, (9/2/1977) (Box > 7)
- BRAVE NEW WORLD (PART I), (4/25/1978) (Box >145)
  Writers: Thompson, Robert E.
- BRAVE NEW WORLD (PART II), (4/24/1978) (Box >145)
- BREAKING HOME TIES, (7/1/1987) (Box > 93)
  Writers: Wilder, John
- BREAKING IN, (no date) (Box > 76)
  Writers: Sayles, John
- BREAKING THE SURFACE, (4/25/1996) (Box >217)
  Writers: Hines, Alan
- BREAKING UP IS HARD TO DO (PART II), (2/9/1979) (Box > 38)
  Writers: Henerson, J.
- BRIAN'S SONG, (7/1/1971) (Box >255)
- BRIDE OF BOOGEDY, (no date) (Box >128)
- BRIDE OF BOOGEDY, (10/1/1986) (Box > 73)
  Writers: Janover, Michael
- BRIDE WORE BLACK (THE), (no date) (Box > 38)
  Writers: Lanzano, A.
- BRINK'S: THE GREAT ROBBERY, (3/26/1976) (Box >152)
- BROKEN PROMISE, (12/31/1980) (Box > 18)
  Writers: Kandel, Stephen
- BROKEN PROMISE, (no date) (Box > 28)
- BROTHERHOOD (THE), (3/2/1990) (Box > 90)
  Writers: Doniger, Walter; Cushnir, Howard
- BROTHERS-IN-LAW (THE), (8/20/1984) (Box > 57)
  Writers: Cannell, Stephen J.
- BUD AND LOU, (5/1/1978) (Box >168)
  Writers: Lefferts, George
- BUD AND LOU, (3/10/1978) (Box > 38)
  Writers: Lefferts, G.
- BUMP IN THE NIGHT, (1/3/1990) (Box >248)
  Writers: Lofton, Christopher
- BUMP IN THE NIGHT, (no date) (Box >125)
- BUNKER (THE), (12/3/1979) (Box > 38)
- BUNNY'S TALE, A, (9/10/1984) (Box >189)
  Writers: Goldstone, Deena
- BURIED ALIVE, (no date) (Box >104)
  Writers: Carducci, Mark Patrick
- BURIED ALIVE, (4/21/1989) (Box >104)
- BURIED ALIVE, (6/23/1989) (Box >104)
- BURIED ALIVE, (8/22/1989) (Box >104)
- BURNING BED (THE), (1/23/1984) (Box > 38)
  Writers: Goldemberg, R.L
- BURNING RAGE, (1/10/1984) (Box >144)
  Writers: Hoeffner, Karol Ann; Campion, Clifford
- BURNING SEASON (THE), (5/17/1994) (Box >202)
- BY DAWN'S EARLY LIGHT, (6/20/1989) (Box >172)
  Writers: Gilbert, Bruce; Franzoni, David
- BY DAWN'S EARLY LIGHT, (1/5/1989) (Box >121)
  Writers: Gilbert, Bruce
- CABO BLANCO, (no date) (Box > 77)
- CALENDAR GIRL MURDERS, (11/2/1983) (Box >169)
  Writers: Swanton, Scott
- CALENDAR GIRL MURDERS, (no date) (Box > 13)
- CALIFORNIA GIRLS, (no date) (Box >218)
- CALIFRONIA GIRLS, (1/1/1984) (Box >190)
  Writers: Rosin, Charles
- CALL OF THE WILD, (no date) (Box >246)
  Writers: Dickey, James
- CALL OF THE WILD (THE), (7/28/1975) (Box >121)
- CALLIE & SON, (11/19/1980) (Box > 18)
  Writers: Thompson, Thomas
- CAMP CUCAMONGA, (1/19/1990) (Box >242)
  Writers: Tramer, Bennett; Melcombe, Rich
- CAMPUS JUSTICE (Released as Silencing Mary, (2/7/1997) (Box >255)
  Writers: Johnson, Steve
- CAN YOU FEEL ME DANCING?, (7/6/1986) (Box >179)
  Writers: Hensley, J. Miyoko; Hensley, Steven
- CAN YOU HEAR THE LAUGHTER?: THE STORY OF FREDDIE, (3/19/1979) (Box >178)
  Writers: Young, Dalene
- CAPRA: WHO SLEW PENDRAGON, (3/17/1978) (Box >197)
  Writers: Fischer, Peter S
- CAPTAIN AVENGER, (3/13/1979) (Box >193)
  Writers: Carothers, A. J.
- CAPTAINS COURAGEOUS, (12/16/1976) (Box >150)
- CAPTAINS COURAGEOUS, (4/5/1977) (Box >193)
- CAROL CHANNING AND ONE HUNDRED AND ONE MEN (SPECIAL), (9/23/1967) (Box >250)
- CARPOOL, (12/30/1982) (Box > 74)
- CARTIER AFFAIR (THE), (3/22/1984) (Box >176)
  Writers: Ross-Leming, Eugenie; Buckner, Brad
- CARTIER HEIST (THE), (4/9/1984) (Box >190)
  Writers: Leming-Ross, Eugenie; Buckner, Brad
- CASINO, (no date) (Box > 28)
- CASSIFIED LOVE, (10/12/1985) (Box >191)
  Writers: English, Diane
- CAST A DEADLY SPELL, (2/1/1988) (Box >183)
  Writers: Dogherty, Joseph
- CAST A DEADLY SPELL, (10/31/1990) (Box >125)
  Writers: Dougherty, Joseph
- CAT CHASER, (no date) (Box > 17)
- CELEBRITY (PART I), (5/20/1983) (Box >194)
  Writers: Hanley, William
- CELEBRITY (PART II), (6/1/1983) (Box >194)
- CELEBRITY (PARTIII), (6/1/1983) (Box >194)
- CELEBRITY (THE), (no date) (Box > 48)
- CELEBRITY HOME VIDEOS, (5/21/1990) (Box > 89)
  Writers: Herskovitz, Marshall; Zwick, Edward
- CENTENNIAL (PART 6 - THE LONGHORNS), (1/12/1978) (Box >133)
- CHARLES AND DIANA: A ROYAL ROMANCE (Released as The Royal Romance of Charles and Diana), (2/26/1982) (Box >256)
  Writers: Freedman, Robert L.; Thompson, Selma
- CHARLESTON, (no date) (Box > 28)
- CHASE (THE), (9/14/1990) (Box >173)
  Writers: Trueblood, Guerdon
- CHERYL LADD...SCENES FROM A SPECIAL, (no date) (Box >237)
  Writers: Wohl, Jack
- CHICAGO STORY, (12/4/1980) (Box >113)
  Writers: Bercovici, Eric
- CHIEFS (PART I), (3/21/1983) (Box >156)
- CHIEFS (PART II), (3/21/1983) (Box >156)
- CHIEFS (PART III), (3/21/1983) (Box >156)
- CHILD OF RAGE, (12/16/1991) (Box >128)
  Writers: Penningroth, Phil
- CHILDREN IN THE CROSSFIRE, (2/24/1984) (Box >140)
  Writers: Chetwynd, Lionel
- CHILDREN OF AN LAC (THE), (5/24/1979) (Box > 97)
  Writers: Hanalis, Blanche
- CHILDREN OF THE DUST, (4/1/1994) (Box >208)
  Writers: Eliason, Joyce
- CHILDREN OF THE NIGHT, (2/19/1985) (Box > 2)
- CHILDREN OF THE NIGHT, (3/15/1983) (Box >170)
  Writers: Silver, Joan Micklin
- CHINA ROSE, (1/1/1983) (Box > 85)
  Writers: Epstein, David
- CHISHOLMS (THE) (PART I), (8/21/1978) (Box >148)
  Writers: Hunter, Evan
- CHISHOLMS (THE) (PART II), (8/21/1978) (Box >148)
- CHISHOLMS (THE) (PART III), (8/22/1978) (Box >148)
- CHRISTIE LOVE (GET), (10/1/1973) (Box >193)
  Writers: Kirgo, George
- CHRISTMAS EVE, (8/12/1986) (Box > 30)
  Writers: HANALIS, BLANCHE
- CHRISTMAS SUNSHINE, (9/1/1977) (Box >201)
- CHRISTOPHER COLUMBUS, (6/25/1983) (Box > 39)
  Writers: Heath, L.
- CHRISTOPHER COLUMBUS, (6/23/1983) (Box > 39)
- CHSING THE DREAM, (8/14/1994) (Box >212)
  Writers: Rhimes, Shonda
- CINDY, (11/2/1977) (Box >116)
  Writers: Brooks, James L.; Daniels, Stan
- CITY IN FEAR (FORMERLY: PANIC ON PAGE ONE), (5/10/1979) (Box >103)
- CITY KILLER, (4/19/1984) (Box >187)
  Writers: Wood, William
- CITY KILLER, (10/4/1983) (Box > 2)
- CLASSIFIED LOVE, (9/12/1985) (Box >210)
- CLINTON AND NADINE, (1/29/1985) (Box >146)
  Writers: Foster, Robert
- CLOVER, (10/9/1996) (Box >220)
  Writers: Cain, Bill; Sanders, Dori
- CLUB MED, (10/14/1985) (Box > 17)
- COCAINE: ONE MAN'S SEDUCTION, (8/27/1982) (Box >161)
  Writers: Schneider, Barry; Goldsmith, David
- CODE RED, (1/8/1982) (Box > 2)
- CODENAME: WOLVERINE, (5/22/1997) (Box >217)
  Writers: Megginson, Robert T.
- COFFEE, TEA OR ME?, (11/18/1972) (Box >119)
  Writers: Panama, Norman; Lewin, Albert E.
- COLD ROOM (THE), (no date) (Box > 78)
  Writers: Derden, James; Caine, Jeffrey
- COLONY (THE), (3/28/1995) (Box >213)
  Writers: Hedden, Rob
- COMBAT HIGH, (8/23/1986) (Box > 90)
  Writers: Shapiro, Paul W.
- COMBAT HIGH, (9/7/1986) (Box > 95)
- COMEBACK (THE), (3/22/1988) (Box >142)
  Writers: Granger, Percy
- COMEBACK KID (THE), (6/14/1979) (Box >175)
  Writers: Landon, Joe
- COMEDY COMPANY, (5/25/1977) (Box >193)
  Writers: Kalcheim, Lee
- COMING OUT OF THE ICE, (6/1/1980) (Box >163)
  Writers: Sharp, Alan
- COMMON GROUND (PARTS I-II), (no date) (Box > 70)
  Writers: Hume, Edward; Lukas, J. Anthony
- COMPANY (THE), (1/10/1989) (Box > 31)
  Writers: BROYLES, JR., WILLIAM
- COMRADES OF SUMMER (THE), (8/3/1990) (Box >183)
  Writers: Rodat, Robert
- COMRADES OF SUMMER (THE), (8/3/1990) (Box >173)
- CONAGHER, (5/10/1990) (Box > 89)
  Writers: Meyer, J.; Elliot, S.; Ross, K.; L'Amour, Louis
- CONFESSIONS OF A MARRIED MAN, (8/26/1982) (Box >181)
  Writers: Gethers, Steven
- CONSENTING ADULT, (6/5/1984) (Box >141)
- CONSENTING ADULT, (7/28/1984) (Box >205)
- CONSPIRACY OF LOVE, A, (3/11/1987) (Box > 29)
  Writers: MORROW, BARRY
- CONTRACT ON CHERRY STREET, (4/26/1977) (Box > 39)
  Writers: Anhalt, E.
- CONUNDRUM, (10/31/1989) (Box >213)
  Writers: Barr, Douglas
- CONUNDRUM, (1/1/1991) (Box >247)
- CONVICT COWBOY, (11/15/1993) (Box >213)
  Writers: Rosenbaum, Henry
- COOK AND PEARY: THE RACE TO THE POLE, (no date) (Box > 39)
  Writers: Clouse, Robert
- COOL MILLION, (9/22/1971) (Box >202)
  Writers: Cohen, Larry
- COPS AND ROBIN (THE), (10/4/1977) (Box >154)
  Writers: Dugan, John T.; Radnitz, Brad
- COREY: FOR THE PEOPLE, (12/2/1976) (Box >147)
  Writers: Boretz, Alvin
- COUGAR!, (5/12/1983) (Box >106)
  Writers: Foreman, Stephen
- COUNTRY GOLD, (6/21/1982) (Box >150)
  Writers: English, Priscilla; Hoeffner, Karol Ann
- COUPLE TAKE A WIFE (THE), (10/9/1972) (Box >201)
  Writers: Silver, Susan
- COVENANT (THE), (2/4/1985) (Box > 77)
  Writers: Feigelson, J. D.; Di Stefano, Dan
- COWBODY AND THE BALLERINA (THE), (4/6/1984) (Box >189)
  Writers: Petitclerc, Denne
- COWBOY, (1/8/1982) (Box > 50)
- CRACKER FACTORY (THE), (9/11/1978) (Box > 99)
- CRASH!, (10/29/1978) (Box > 25)
  Writers: Williams, H.
- CRASH: THE TRUE STORY OF FLIGHT 401, (4/13/1978) (Box > 78)
  Writers: Brown, Steve; Sanford, Donald S.
- CRASH: THE TRUE STORY OF FLIGHT 401, (7/10/1978) (Box >164)
- CRAZY TIMES, (9/8/1980) (Box > 78)
  Writers: Reeves, George
- CRIME OF INNOCENCE, (8/1/1985) (Box >112)
  Writers: Berk, Michael; Schwartz, Douglas
- CRIME OF THE CENTURY, (2/26/1996) (Box >240)
  Writers: Nicholson, William
- CRIME OF THE CENTURY, (6/27/1995) (Box >254)
- CRISIS AT CENTRAL HIGH, (4/14/1980) (Box >168)
  Writers: Levinson, Richard; Link, William
- CRISIS AT CENTRAL HIGH, (6/8/1979) (Box >178)
- CRISIS IN MID-AIR, (9/26/1978) (Box > 39)
  Writers: Bache, S.
- CRISIS IN SUN VALLEY, (12/13/1976) (Box >124)
  Writers: Gottlieb, Carl
- CRO-MAGNON, (2/15/1974) (Box >203)
- CROOKED HEARTS (THE), (5/3/1972) (Box >111)
  Writers: Russell, A.J.
- CROSS OF FIRE (PARTS I AND II), (3/31/1989) (Box > 67)
  Writers: Crais, Robert
- CROSSFIRE, (11/26/1974) (Box >148)
  Writers: Saltzman, Philip
- CROSSING THE MOB, (2/14/1985) (Box >212)
  Writers: Colick, Lewis
- CROWFOOT, (no date) (Box >244)
  Writers: Bellisario, Donald
- CRUISE INTO TERROR, (11/18/1977) (Box >109)
  Writers: Braverman, Michael
- CRUISE INTO TERROR, (10/5/1977) (Box >241)
- CRY FOR LOVE, A, (3/4/1980) (Box >157)
  Writers: Taylor, Renee; Bologna, Joseph
- CRY FOR THE STRANGERS, (11/6/1981) (Box > 69)
  Writers: Feigelson, J. D.; Saul, John
- CRY FOR THE STRANGERS, (11/6/1981) (Box >256)
  Writers: Feigelson, J.D.
- CRY PANIC, (11/2/1973) (Box >122)
  Writers: Sowards, Jack B.
- CRY RAPE!, (9/5/1973) (Box >119)
  Writers: Lorin, Will
- CURIOUSITY KILLS, (2/8/1990) (Box >104)
  Writers: Batteer, Joe; Rice, John
- CURSE OF THE BLACK WIDOW, (3/8/1977) (Box >107)
  Writers: Blees, Robert; Wallace, Earl W.
- DAD (THE) ANGEL, AND ME, (6/13/1994) (Box >247)
  Writers: Goldstein, Josh
- DADDY, (2/17/1987) (Box > 17)
- DAIN CURSE (THE) (PART I), (8/30/1977) (Box >180)
  Writers: Lenski, Robert W.; Hammett, Dashiell
- DAIN CURSE (THE) (PART II), (8/30/1977) (Box >180)
- DALLAS COWBOYS CHEERLEADERS, (10/17/1978) (Box >116)
  Writers: Hamner, Robert
- DALLAS COWBOYS CHEERLEADERS II, (10/26/1979) (Box >196)
- DALVA, (no date) (Box >245)
  Writers: Mitchell, Judith Paige
- DAMIEN... THE LEPER PRIEST, (1/14/1979) (Box >111)
  Writers: Hanley, William; Presnell, Jr., Robert
- DANCING IN THE DARK, (4/26/1994) (Box >208)
  Writers: Feather, Jacqueline; Seidler, David
- DANGEROUS COMPANY, (9/16/1981) (Box > 77)
  Writers: Keane, Christopher; Johnson, Ray
- DANGEROUS RELATIONS, (10/21/1991) (Box >207)
  Writers: Davis, Walter Halsey
- DANIELLE STEEL'S FINE THINGS, (4/9/1990) (Box >138)